[Music]
hi
and welcome back to 5 shake this video
is another haagen-dazs one
now in the uk this flavor used to be
called chocolate midnight cookies and it
was my favorite haagen-dazs flavor they
ever made
and it disappeared off the shelves years
ago but it turns out in the u.s it had
two
other names one was midnight cookies and
cream
and then again that disappeared off the
shelves and it's now become a fan
request
and it's called i forgot to look up
because i can't remember too many names
is triple chocolate fudge cookie
thankfully haagen-dazs put the
ingredients on their website
and as they're all custard-based ice
creams they're pretty easy to follow the
only thing that isn't easy to follow
is the fudge but we will do our best and
see how we get on
[Music]
so this base is actually quite simple
we're not going to temper eggs like
a lot of people do we're going to put
the egg yolks straight into the pan
with all your other ingredients apart
from your cocoa
slowly bring it up between 80 and 85
degrees c
and that will sort your eggs out without
the need to temper them in a slightly
more confusing way
then add your cocoa combine all well and
put it in a container now obviously at
this point you can add any ingredients
you forgot like i did such as the
vanilla
and then cover it and put it in your
fridge overnight
[Music]
the fudge well for this was a bit of a
guess
i decided to wing it as there are no
numbers
from haagen-dazs anywhere on the
internet now for this
i just combined the milk and cocoa in a
pan and just gently combined it over
some heat
at that point i added the corn syrup and
the coconut oil
and as you can see it just started to
separate slightly but just keep going
bear with it
get it up to a rolling boil and turn off
the heat
and then finally add in your chocolate
and stir it well to combine
once that's ready pop it in a container
and leave it to cool to room temperature
[Music]
to when your ice cream is ready to churn
take it out your fridge and pop it in
your machine
whilst it's churning you can prepare
your cookies now in this ice cream
they make their own cookies but
essentially they're just oreos
but there is no oreo cream so take your
pack of oreos
and gently remove all the cream from
there chop them up
put them aside ready for later
[Music]
uh
once your ice cream is ready to batch up
start loading into your tub
and layer in your cookie pieces and your
fudge swirl until it's
all looking lovely and full and pop it
in the freezer
for a few hours until it's ready to eat
[Music]
oh
out the freezer and then if you can see
it in focus or not i'll put a bigger
picture up
on the screen great tub from my wife
again
let's get some scooped up and see how
this one's turned out shall we
[Music]
first things first it looks great you
can see obviously the fudge
coming out there it's nice and soft big
chunks of cookie there
looking forward to this one this like i
said this was my favorite haagen-dazs
when it was available so
i hope it tastes good let's see
[Music]
hmm that's really good
now the fudge isn't identical to how it
used to be
i think i've probably used a little bit
too much cocoa
i mean not for me it tastes great in
comparison to
to the haagen-dazs one because there's
no numbers to follow
you just gotta take a bit of a punt and
see how it turns out
but it's a really good combo you've got
the dark chocolate ice cream
got a really nice fudge swirl it's soft
it's decadent
it's real punch of chocolate to it as
well and those little oreo pieces
without the cream
it's nice it doesn't overpower so it's a
really lovely combo
midnight cookies and cream chocolate
midnight cookies
chocolate fudge cookie swirl
stuff and things there's so many names
for this i don't know what to call it
but if you like cookies and cream if you
like chocolate if you like fudge
go for this and give it a bash it's a
really really good one so
i'm just gonna eat this it's pretty
early actually it's
quarter to nine in the morning so ice
cream for breakfast anyone